{
    "id": "f8f4e8fd6d014e84b096df2be82e6844",
    "title": "High School Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget, ………………………..?",
            "description": "After a negative imperative we use will you in question tags.",
            "answers": [
                "won't you",
                "can you",
                "will you"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e031b0e1a98b47ac9dc2b5fd43426cb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have got six children ……………………….. are studying music.",
            "description": "Either structure is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "all of whom",
                "of whom all",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3e8226e28a3d40b09938884ca0a5a111"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget the day ………………………….. we met.",
            "description": "After nouns referring to time we can use that instead of when.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "when",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9899433406894279b1ef1cceac545754"
        },
        {
            "question": "The reason ……………………………… I dislike you is that you are so bad-tempered.",
            "description": "Either why or that can be used after that.",
            "answers": [
                "why",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "352a181c8a5f4e5f873e2ccf974dc48a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please remind me …………………………. the oil.",
            "description": "Remind is followed by object + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "to check",
                "checking",
                "of checking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11d8009c3147427ba45ff15a2b9b6893"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. me that we hadn’t bought anything to eat.",
            "description": "To remind somebody is to make them remember.",
            "answers": [
                "reminded",
                "remembered",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c4fc1322a0047a98e8be1ade42916da"
        },
        {
            "question": "You remind me ……………………………… I had met at school.",
            "description": "Of is required in this structure.",
            "answers": [
                "a girl",
                "of a girl"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a1c6d2a68b843bc9fe489be0a0f508b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a stern man who always ………………………………. me of my headmaster.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reminds",
                "remembers",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9fee8ed705174e9bae50d6c9ba2fbf6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is a kind woman who always makes me ……………………………. my grandmother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "remind",
                "remember",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02d0697bcd9d4517ae3be3fab99875cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He suggested …………………………… the main car park.",
            "description": "We cannot use an infinitive after suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "me to use",
                "me using",
                "that I use"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "69c7da5105ff4ec4b6006f2c5c1e5e56"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said ……………………………….. park there.",
            "description": "We use a that-clause after said.",
            "answers": [
                "me not to",
                "that I must not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3e4588d9e2a84ba9aa53c3dda34d4792"
        },
        {
            "question": "He told ……………………………",
            "description": "Tell can be followed by object + infinitive or object + that clause.",
            "answers": [
                "me to wait",
                "me that I should wait",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a2c54f01bf5340a294a9549507463a6e"
        }
    ]
}